[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
on that leadership
congratulations
and the families
members and all the leadership
Associates for their dedication and
their 14 setting up this impressive
facility
through this new facility we aim to
cater to give Honda's Premium Power
buying experience and exceed their
expectations in every way possible
our focus is to Pro provide perfect
combination of Premium products and it's
exceptional customer service to our
customers
is all of you to follow this premium
approach in your day-to-day operations
and they ensure that your facility
facility is best in your town
the opening of this new leadership comes
at an exciting time
when we are getting ready to launch our
brand new SUV home database
we have just started the bus production
available and soon you will start
receiving the cars at your leadership
[Music]
another time